<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello Friend</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there My name is Radek and I&amp;rsquo;m the author of this theme. I made it to help you present your ideas easier.
We all know how hard is to start something on the web, especially these days. You need to prepare a bunch of stuff, configure them and when that’s done — create the content.
This theme is pretty basic and covers all of the essentials. All you have to do is start typing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Header 2 Backup two-step verification breach, anonymous terminal traffic worm virus reboot fsociety dat file. Traffic fsociety malware 100 terabytes system hack, delete brute-force cyber security fiber connection connect code worm wipe. Cyber security off the grid delete IP decrypt, nodes connect password 100 terabytes RUDY attack malicious code rootkit gigabit speed. Tor connect network, intercepting traffic off the grid IP protocol password.
 Backup DDoS attack rootkit nodes disconnect website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>Hello Worldcode{white-space: pre;}pre:not([class]) {background-color: white;}if (window.hljs) {hljs.configure({languages: []});hljs.initHighlightingOnLoad();if (document.readyState &amp;&amp; document.readyState === &#34;complete&#34;) {window.setTimeout(function() { hljs.initHighlighting(); }, 0);}}h1 {font-size: 34px;}h1.title {font-size: 38px;}h2 {font-size: 30px;}h3 {font-size: 24px;}h4 {font-size: 18px;}h5 {font-size: 16px;}h6 {font-size: 12px;}.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Friend</title>
      <link>/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 1986 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;Hello, friend?&amp;rdquo; That&amp;rsquo;s lame. Maybe I should give you a name&amp;hellip;
But that&amp;rsquo;s a slippery slope.
You&amp;rsquo;re only in my head.
We have to remember that&amp;hellip;
Shit.
It&amp;rsquo;s actually happened.
I&amp;rsquo;m talking to an imaginary person.
— Mr. Robot S01E01
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood</title>
      <link>/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post1/</guid>
      <description>Villain or CriminalI recently re-watched Now You See Me both 1 and 2. In watching them I could not help but draw parallel references to the Robin Hood nature of the protagonists. So for those who do not what Now You See Me is about I will give you a summary.
Now You See Me is a crime film about a guy’s 30 year retribution plan against the people who helped kill his father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking a Bite Out of My Apple</title>
      <link>/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>Over the last couple of years, there have been many court cases between US law enforcement and private companies. These cases are often over issues of privacy where government agencies want access to someone’s messages or phones. In most of these cases, the communication company wins. Specifically, in 2016, Apple and the FBI went to court over the FBI’s demand that Apple creates a software giving the FBI access to phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking a Bite Out of My Apple</title>
      <link>/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE)  Over the last couple of years, there have been many court cases between US law enforcement and private companies. These cases are often over issues of privacy where government agencies want access to someone&amp;rsquo;s messages or phones. In most of these cases, the communication company wins. Specifically, in 2016, Apple and the FBI went to court over the FBI&amp;rsquo;s demand that Apple creates a software giving the FBI access to phones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>